Washington Women's Arts Center 004
DCPL Special Collections - MLK Library
- Series 4: Financial Records, 1975-1978
  - D.C. Commission Grant Proposal, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - D.C. Commission Grant- Awarded $10,000, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - D.C. Commission on Arts and Humanities Grant Application, FY 1986 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - D.C. Commission on Arts and Humanities Grant Application, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Payment Request- Second Half Of, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Letters of Support, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - D.C. Commission on Arts and Humanities grant Application, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Statement of Earnings, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - D.C. Commission- 616 E St, 1986- 1987 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - D.C. Commission Grant- Application Grant Transmitted, October 1 1986- September 15 1987 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Payment Request (D.C. Funds) for Second Half of Fiscal Year 1988 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - D.C. Commission Narrative Report, FY 1987 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - D.C. Commission Application Materials, FY 1988 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - D.C. Commission Applications and Background, FY 1988- 1989 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Unlabeled Folder: postcards, 1989 DC Commission on the Arts and Humanities Grant application, Letters of Support, Undated (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Tina Lunson/ WWAC Agreement, September 1982 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Receipts and Expenses, 1979-1980 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Accounts, ca 1982 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Art Sales, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Sales: Policy and Forms- Q St- 25% Commission, Undated (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Birth Project- Book Sales, Undated (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Talleys- Behalf of Artists Gallery Sales, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Tally Forms/ Petty Cash, Undated (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Petty Cash Receipts: Sylvia Snowden- Gallery Coordinator, FY 1984 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Petty Cash Receipts: Kitty Bahnsen- Exhibitions Committee, FY 1984 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Petty Cash, 1981- April 1983 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Quill Purchases, Undated (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Beaver Press (Newsletter), Undated (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Ads, 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Ad Rates, 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Bulk Mailing/ Postage Present, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - WWAC Financial Records- IRS - Misc, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - WWAC Financial Records- Misc. Papers, Undated (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - WWAC Receipts, January 1975-December 1975 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - WWAC Receipts, January 1976-December 1976 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - WWAC Receipts, January 1977-December 1977 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - WWAC Receipts, January 1978-June 1978 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - WWAC Receipts, July 1978-December 1978 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - WWAC Receipts, January 1979-June 1979 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - WWAC Receipts, July 1979-December 1979 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - WWAC Receipts, January 1980-June 1980 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - WWAC Receipts, July 1980-December 1980 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - WWAC Receipts, January 1981-June 1981 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - A, Undated (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - B, Undated (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Bahsen, Undated (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Barnes, Undated (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Becker, Undated (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - C, Undated (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - D, Undated (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - D.C. Postmaster, Undated (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - E, Undated (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - F, Undated (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - G, Undated (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Gordon, Undated (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - H, Undated (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - I, Undated (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Insta-Print, Undated (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - J, Undated (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - K, Undated (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Kragh, Undated (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - L, Undated (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Litwak, Undated (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - M, Undated (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Marketpeace, Undated (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - N, Undated (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Northern Virginia Sun, Undated (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - O, Undated (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Stories, Undated (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Pessa, Undated (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - Q, Undated (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - R, Undated (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - S, Undated (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - T, Undated (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - U, Undated (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - V, Undated (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - W, Undated (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - Wells, Undated (Box 40, Folder 35)
  - X, Undated (Box 40, Folder 36)
  - Y, Undated (Box 40, Folder 37)
  - Z, Undated (Box 40, Folder 38)
  - WWAC Receipts, January 1984-December 1984 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - WWAC Receipts, January 1985-December 1985 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - WWAC Receipts, August 1986- June 1987 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - WWAC Receipts, January 1986-December 1986 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - WWAC Receipts, January 1987-December 1987 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - WWAC Receipts, January 1988-July 1988 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - WWAC Financial Records Receipts Misc., 1985-1986 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Cash Day Book, 1980- 1984 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Past Receipts, Undated (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Sales Receipts, 1978-1979 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Income and Expenditures, September 1978- August 1979 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - WWAC Arts For Gifts Sale Book, 1982 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - WWAC Arts For Gifts Sales Misc., 1982 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Cash Records- Partial, 1975-1976 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Deposit Detail Sheets, July 1977- August 1978 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Deposit Detail Sheets, August 1978- December 1979 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Cash Receipts- Deposit Ledgers, September 1980- August 1981 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Financial Records Deposit Sheet, January- August 1980 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Deposit Ledgers, September 1981- January 1982 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Deposit Ledgers, February 1982- August 1982 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Record of Cash Receipts- Deposit Ledgers, September- October 1982 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Series 5: Membership and Guest books, 1977-1987
  Contains records which document individuals which supported and attended the Center's activities, including membership directories, guest books for Center events, an address book (1980), card index of active members (1987), and cards index of inactive members (1988).
  - Receipt Book for Sales and Membership, 1986-1988 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Membership List, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Membership List, 1979-1980 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Membership List, April 1980-June 1981 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Membership Programs, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Membership Lists, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Guest Book (Several Exhibits), 1983-1984 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Guest Book (Political Art Show only), July 1984 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Guest Book (Exhibits unspecified), 1985-1986 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Guest Book (Exhibits unspecified), 1987-1988 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Rubber Stamp- New Art Center, 6925 Willow St N.W., Undated (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Rubber Stamp- For Deposit Only, New Art Center, Undated (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Membership Lists, Card Catalog (On Index Cards), Undated (Box 51, Folder 1)
- Series 6: Newsletters, 1975-1981
  This series contains copies of the Center's newsletter, "WWAC News."
  - Newsletter Articles/Copies/Ads, 1975 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Newsletter Various Issues, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Newsletter (includes telephone list of key personnel), 1977 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Newsletter, 1978 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Newsletter, 1978-1979 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Newsletter, 1979-1980 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Newsletter, 1980-1981 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Newsletter, 1987-1988 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Newsletter, 1979-1980 (Box 57, Folder 2)
- Series 7: Exhibitions Files, 1975-1988
  Contains materials, which document the preparation and publicity for exhibitions at the Center. Materials are arranged under three subseries.
  - Subseries 1: Office files, 1975-1988
    Exhibition office files which contain correspondence, handwritten lists, contracts, clippings, publicity, some photographs, and resumes between the Center and the artist as well as others involved in planning for exhibitions.
    - Sculptors' Show, April 1975 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Feminine Erotica, 1975 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Report for Mothers Day Show (First Annual), Undated (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Members Show, June 1975 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Photo Show - September 14, 1975 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Elise Asher, February- March 1976 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Georgina Beier, April 25- May 23 1976 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Member Show, March 21 1976 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Five- Part Series Exhibit (Undated) (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Show and Tell (Workshops) - Exhibit, June 5- June 27 1976 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Monday Mornings, July 12 1976 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - One to One, 1976 (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Let's Face It- Photography Show (Photos in folder), October 26- November 27 1976 (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Dimensionally Speaking, November 30- December 26 1976 (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Religious Imagery and Self Portrait Show, December 1975 (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - The Eye of Davenport, January 18- February 20 1977 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Yvonne Center Show, February 1977 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - From the Center, 1977 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - From the Center traveling, April 1- July 30 1977 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - La Reche and Young (Photos in Folder), 1977 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Workshops Show and Tell Exhibits, June 5- June 26 1977 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Alternate Spaces, July 20- September 16 1977 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - New Faces, July 1977 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Positives Photography Show, September 20- October 8 1977 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - New Answers- Afterwards at Kramer Books, 1977 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Fiber Show, 1977 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Fiber Art, November 1977 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - 13 Answers, May 1977 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - 13 Answers, Undated (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Sculpture Show, October 1977 (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - Art for Gifts Sake, November 27- December 23 1977 (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - 4 Person Show, January 1978 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Alternate Space/ Gallery Maggie, March 1978 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Shows in Alternate Spaces for Women, 1978 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Works With Paper, March 1978 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Print Makers Show, April 1978 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - As Women See It, June 1978 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Fourteen Hangups, May 1978 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - New Faces Show, June 1978 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Workshop Show: A Look at Workshops, June 1978 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Black and White Show, October 1978 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Art for Gifts Sake, 1978 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Eleanor Dickinson, 1978 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Eye of Yvonne Carter, February 1978 (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Center Information, 1977-1978 (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - WWAC Info, 1978 (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Paint Show, September 1978 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Painting Show, Fall 1978 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Creative Line Show, November 1978 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Eye of Miriam Schapiro, January 1979 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Limitations Unlimited, February 1979 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Private Spaces, February 27- March 17 1979 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Almost Impossible, March 20- April 7 1979 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Artemesia Show (Exhibit slides in folder), May 1979 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - New Faces Show, July 1979 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Painting and Sculpture, October 1979 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - AROW - Exchange Show (exhibit slides in folder), April 1979 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Clay and Line, September 1979 (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - Portraits for Alice Neel, 1979-1981 (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - WWAC Space Adopt, Undated (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Front Page Exchange Show, January 1980 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Hartigan Show- Chairperson Info, February 1980 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Feminist show, March 1980 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - National Conference of Artists Exhibition, April 1980 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Printmakers Show III, 1980 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Fiber Show, September 1980 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Founders Show, October 1980 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Anything but Papers, 1980 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Exhibition Books, May 1981 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Five Person Show Info, June 1984 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Best of 85 Sculpture Show, April 1985 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Birth/Creation Show, April 30-June 1985 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Salon Des Refuses, June 1985 (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Photography Show, July 1985 (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Reflection of Washington, September 1985 (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - Area Wide Show, October 1985 (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - Printmakers VII, October 29-November 23 1985 (Box 62, Folder 17)
    - Craft Show, November 26-December 14 1985 (Box 62, Folder 18)
    - Works on Paper, January 7- February 1 1986 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Works on Paper: Fire Damage, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Let the Arts Be First, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Sculpture, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Women and Power, April 1986 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Interiors/Exteriors, May 1986 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Celebration and Rituals- Betsy Damon - Juror, June 10- July 2 1986 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - The Aesthetic Text, September 1986 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Aesthetic Text- Fundraising, Undated (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Figurative Work, October 1986 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Printmakers VIII, October 29- November 23 1986 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Craft Show, December 1986 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Betty Branch, Undated (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Equipment, Undated (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - Member's Skills, Undated (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - Grants for Sculpture, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 16)
    - Emerging Artists Show, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Ethnic Vibrations, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Wear Our Heart on Your Sleeve Photo Exhibit, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Jazz, February 1987 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Eat Your Art Out, February 1987 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Sculpture Through Touch (Catritz Grant), 1987 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Scapes: City, Land, and Sea, April 1987 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Viewing Ourselves, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Feminism Show, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Board Show, June 1987 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Ruth Weiler Craig Show, June 1987 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Art of Craft: The Fine Line, July 1987 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - ADD Arts Festival, September 1987 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Collage, October 1987 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Abstractions, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Printmakers IX, November 1987 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Feminism, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Contemporary Viewpoints: Craft in Our Changing World, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Ragtime Entries, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - December Craft Show, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Collectors' Draws, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Collectors' Draws: Schedules and Duties, 1986-1987 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Collectors' Draw, 1986 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Wall to Wall fundraiser Show, February 1983 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Birthproject Fundraiser, 1985 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Artist and the Guilt - Booksales Fundraiser, November 1983 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Membership Applications, 1985 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Auction Entry Blanks, 1984 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Art Auction Fundraiser, June 8 1984 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - TNAC Correspondence, 1988 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Artist Outreach, 1986 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Forms, Undated (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Outreach Artist Agreement, Undated (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Artist Outreach Exhibition Records, 1986 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Artist Outreach Registration Form- Mechanicals, 1986-1987 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Alternative Space- GSA, 1977-1978 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Alternative Space- Defense Documentation Center, 1977-1978 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Alternative Space Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Alternative Space- Lansburgh, 1981-1982 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Alternative Space- Insurance, 1982-1983 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Alternative Spaces, 1985-1986 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Alternative Space Contacts, 1986 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Alternative Spaces, 1980-1981 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Alternative Spaces- Receipt of Work Form, Undated (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Alternative Space Forms, 1982-1983 (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - Sales of Artwork- Interim Policy, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - Coordinator's Checklist, Undated (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Photographer Contacts, Undated (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Washington Area Lawyers for the Arts Package, Undated (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Exhibition Receiving Instructions, 1987 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Individual/Group Exhibit Acceptance Letter, Undated (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Artist's Responsibilities for Group Shows, Undated (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Artist Slide Submission- Letter of Regret, Undated (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Individual or Group Exhibit- Letter of Regret, Undated (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Exhibitions -Appointment Calendar, 1987 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Juror Confirmation Follow Up/ Gallery Talk Invitation, Undated (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Artist Slide Submission, Undated (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Juror Info Response Form, Undated (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Artist Slide Submission, Undated (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - Exhibition Committee- Letter of Notice for Meeting, Undated (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - Letter to Barbara Luther, Undated (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - Juror Confirmation Letter, Undated (Box 69, Folder 16)
    - Juror Addresses, Undated (Box 69, Folder 17)
    - Juror Resumes, Undated (Box 69, Folder 18)
    - Call for Entries, 1986-1987 (Box 69, Folder 19)
    - Group Shows/ One Person Gallery Exhibit Space, 1987 (Box 69, Folder 20)
    - Sculpture Entries, 1988 (Box 69, Folder 21)
    - Gallery Letters- Notebooks, 1986-1987 (Box 69, Folder 22)
    - Misc. Exhibition Info, Undated (Box 69, Folder 23)
    - Interesting Publicity, Undated (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - PR Lists, 1982 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Artists' Acceptance Fee, 1986-1987 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Budget, Undated (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Calls for Entry- Past Shows, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Committee Assignments, Undated (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Exhibition Entry Forms, Undated (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Entry Forms- Slides (master copy), Undated (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Exhibition List, October 1977-April 1983 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Gallery Rental, 1984 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Gallery Sitter Calendar (blank), Undated (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Opening Reception Food/Wine Sign Up Forms, Undated (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - WWAC Photographers, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - Press Releases, 1986, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - Printers Prices, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 15)
    - Accepted Works Checklist (blank), Undated (Box 70, Folder 16)
    - Forms for Advance PR Information, Undated (Box 70, Folder 17)
    - Gallery Sitters- Reserve List (blank), Undated (Box 70, Folder 18)
    - Sales Policy- Q St, Undated (Box 70, Folder 19)
    - Exhibitions Schedule, 1986, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 20)
    - Show Entry Forms (master), Undated (Box 70, Folder 21)
    - Work Removal Notices- 21 Days after show, Undated (Box 70, Folder 22)
  - Subseries 2: Notebooks, 1977-1985
    Loose-leaf notebooks of all final documentation on each exhibit. They contain photographs, correspondence, resumes, lists of items in exhibitions, slides, and clips from the publications, including the Center's newsletter, Womansphere, and Artist Outreach.
    - Four Person Show, 1977 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Positives: Photographs, September 20- October 8 1977 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Fiber Art, November 1977 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - The Eye of Yvonne Carter, February 7- March 4 1978 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Printmakers Show, April 1978 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - 14 Hang-Ups, May 1978 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - New Faces, June 27- July 22 1978 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Creative Line Show, November 1978 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Art for Gifts Sake- Resumes, 1979 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Private Spaces: Photography, February 27- March 17 1979 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Exchange Show at AROW (Schenectady NY), April 1979 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Final Draft: 3RD Annual Show Art World Seminars, May 1979 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Painting and Sculpture, October 1979 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Second Annual Printmakers Show, October 30-November 24 1979 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Art for Gifts Sake, November 26- December 23 1979 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Eye of Hartigan, January 29- February 23 1980 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Feminist Art: Process and Product, February 26- March 22 1980 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Art World, May 13-31 1980 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Printmakers Show III, October 28- November 29 1980 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Portraits for Alice Neel, January 6-24 1981 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - The Eye of May Stevens, January 27- February 21 1981 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Woman's Tools, February 24-March 21 1981 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Photography '81, March 24-April 11 1981 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Art World V, May 12-30 1981 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Exchange Exhibition, June 1981 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Thirty-two Pieces of Paper, June 2-27 1981 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Art '81, September 9-14 1981 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Collage and Drawing, September 8-30 1981 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Islands I Have Known and Loved: Postcards, October 27- November 21 1981 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Powerhouse, 1981 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Eye of Eleanor Munro, January 5-23 1982 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Erotic Art Show, January 26- February 20 1982 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Love Notes/ Erotic Postcards, January 26- February 20 1982 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Printmakers IV, February 23-March 20 1982 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Fiber '82: Miniatures, April 13-May 8 1982 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Woman As Myth and Archetype, May 11-29 1982 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Sculpture '82, June 1-26 1982 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Talking Pictures: Collaborations Between Visual and Literary Artists, September 7- October 2 1982 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - The Poem is the Last Resort- Photography, November 2-21 1982 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Art for Gifts Sake, November 30- December 22 1982 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - First Annual WWAC Dog Show, 1982 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Backgrounds, February 8-26 1983 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - The Eye of Adelyn Breeskin, 1983 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Shapes and Textures, April 5-30 1983 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Decorative Arts Show, May 3-27 1983 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Printmakers V, May 31-June 24 1983 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Mini-Maxi, June 28-July 23 1983 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Painter's Choice Exhibit, September 1983 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Landscapes, October 4-29 1983 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Dreams and Daydreams, November 1-26 1983 (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Water Exhibit, January 31-February 25 1984 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - The Goddess Show, February 28-March 31 1984 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - The Eye of Willem De Looper, April 3-28 1984 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - 5-4-5, June 12-30 1984 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Political Art Show in July, July 10-28 1984 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - The Artist in the Art, September 11-29 1984 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Things that Go Bump in the Night, October 2-27 1984 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Printmakers Show VI, November 1-30 1984 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - 10-Day Open, December 4-15 1984 (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Personal Expression: Sculpture, 1984 (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Patterning and Sequential Imagery, February 5-March 5 1985 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - The Best of '85 Sculpture, April 2-27 1985 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Creation/Birth Show, April 30-June 1 1985 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Salon Des Refuses, June 4-29 1985 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Photography, July 2-26 1985 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Reflections of Washington, September 1-28 1985 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Area- wide Juried Show, October 1-26 1985 (Box 91, Folder 3)